locogringo.com 2015-09-05

# LocoGringo Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Loco Gringo Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://www.locogringo.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Loco Gringo Inc..

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### How we use collected information

Loco Gringo Inc. may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * **To improve customer service**  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * **To personalize user experience**  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * **To improve our Site**  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * **To process payments**  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * **To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site features**  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * **To send periodic emails**  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

### Changes to this privacy policy

Loco Gringo Inc. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

**Loco Gringo Inc.**

http://www.locogringo.com

619 New York Ave.  
Claymont DE 19703  
In Mexico: Lote 74 H Akumal, QR Mexico 77769  
52-984-875-9140  

##### _This document was last updated on July 29, 2013_

### Get Your Vacation Vibe™ On

Get the inside scoop, hot tips, little known secrets and DEALS for the Riviera Maya, Costa Maya & Yucatan

#### Tell us where to send your good Vacation Vibe:

### Your Inquiry

#### Jumpstart your next amazing vacation

### Tell Us About Your Vacation

* Denotes A Required Field

* *

I must have these exact dates. *

### Tell Us About You

* * * * *

### Get everything you want in your vacation.

#### Describe your vision for your Riviera Maya vacation.

#### Check all that apply:

Swim with the turtles Pampered at the spa Local cuisine Ziplines & adventure tours Nightlife and dancing Romantic beach dinners Local Shopping

Beach bars World class golf Stomping Mayan ruins Hanging on the beach Private chef service Diving and snorkeling Sportfishing

#### Occasion:

Wedding Family Reunion Birthday Honeymoon Anniversary

To help us find the BEST place for you, what are you planning to spend for your place to stay?

Have you booked with Locogringo before?*

Yes

No

Yes, I would like to receive _Vacation Vibe_ each month.
